

Lorena Macri

About me

My enthusiasm for technology is reflected in my constant pursuit of knowledge, with ease in adapting to various tools and interfaces, putting my skills into practice. I take the initiative to learn and expand my knowledge

Contact



+54-1136725192



lorenamicaela31@gmail.com



Ezeiza, Buenos Aires, Argentina

More information

total hourly availability.

- .Effective Communication
- Experience taking leadership in projects.

Experience

Tour Guide, Tour Bus

Travel Agency | September 2019 - January 2020

- Assertive English and Spanish communication with foreigner visitors.
- Ensured a positive and informative environment.
- First Aids training.

Customer Service and Stock Manager

ISaint Mary's Institute. | July 2021 - December 2021

- -Online stock administration
- Daily cash register

Enlgish Language Professor

Freelance | December 2020- Present

-Conducted English language classes for college students

Education

Ezeiza's Natiional University

Software Developer | March 2022 - Present

Lenguas Vivas Institute

Higher English preparation | 2015 - 2019

-Proficiency level C1

Front-End Developer

Web Development | September 2023 - Present

- HTML, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, JavaScrip

Languages

Spanish

Native.

English

Proficient English level C1.